Guide to the Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature, 1936-2014 and undated RL.00045
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Anspach Travel Bureau collection of tourism literature
1936-2014 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Anspach Travel Bureau
RL.00045
60 Linear Feet 50,000 items
Real estate and travel company founded in 1932 by brothers Herman and Robert Anspach in Highland Park, Ill. Currently part of Valerie Wilson Travel, Inc. Collection spans 1936-2014 with the bulk of materials dating from the 1960s-1980s. Primarily brochures, leaflets and other take-away direct marketing materials advertising resorts, hotels, airlines, cruise lines, and other services and destinations comprising the travel and tourism industry. Also includes newsletters, itineraries, and some correspondence. All continents and ocean regions are represented. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2012 and 2014.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1936-2014 with the bulk of materials dating from the 1960s-1980s. Primarily brochures, leaflets and other take-away direct marketing materials advertising resorts, hotels, airlines, cruise lines, and other services and destinations comprising the travel and tourism industry. Also includes newsletters, itineraries, and some correspondence. All continents and ocean regions are represented. The bulk of the collection is in English, but some of the items are multi-lingual or in the native language of country of origin. Spanish, French, German, Russian, Japanese, Chinese, and Pidgin English among other languages, are represented in the collection
Collection Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by region.
Related Material
Related material can be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Advertising Ephemera Collection
Charles McKinney Papers
Henry Haberman Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Chicago Office Non-Proprietary Research Reports
J. Walter Thompson Company Corporation Vertical Files
J. Walter Thompson Company Eleanor Newman Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company New Business Records
Jacqueline End Papers
Wunderman Archives
Cruise lines; Advertising -- Tourism; Hotels; Direct marketing; Advertising -- Hotels; Brochures; Illinois; Travel; Resorts; Travel agents -- United States; Travel agents -- Illinois; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Anspach Travel Bureau
- General Files, 1959-2006 and undated; 1; 10 boxes
  - General Files, 1
    - Capers Club, 1971-1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Cesia Travel Service, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Club Med, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Cruises, 1966-1975 and undated (Box 1)
    - Examples of English Notices Posted Overseas (Richard Lederer), undated (Box 1)
    - Joseph Edmund, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
    - Lindblad Explorer, 1981-1983 and undated (Box 1)
    - Northwest Orient Tours, undated (Box 1)
    - Society Expeditions, 1982-1985 (Box 1)
    - Swan Hellenic, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - William D. Buckman's Travel Time, 1983-1985 (Box 1)
  - Hotel Directories, 2
    - A-E, 1988-2005 and undated (Box 1)
    - F, 2003 and undated (Box 2)
    - Four Seasons, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
    - G-K, 1986-2003 and undated (Box 2)
    - Leading Hotels of the World, 1994-1999 (Box 2)
    - M, 1987-2004 and undated (Box 2)
    - Mandarin Oriental, 1982-2002 (Box 2)
    - N-O, 1983-2005 (Box 2)
    - Orient Express, 1985-2005 (Box 2)
    - P, 1971-2004 and undated (Box 2)
    - Peninsula, 1995-2004 (Box 2)
    - Pride of Britain, 2003-2004 and undated (Box 3)
    - R, 2003 and undated (Box 3)
    - Relais & Chateaux, 1985 and undated (Box 3)
    - Ritz-Carlton, 1998-2003 (Box 3)
    - Rosewood, 2003-2005 and undated (Box 3)
    - S, 2003 and undated (Box 3)
    - Sheraton, undated (Box 3)
    - Small Luxury Hotels, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
    - Starwood, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
    - U.S. Tour Operators Association, 2004 (Box 3)
    - V-W, 1989-2002 (Box 4)
    - Virtuoso, 2004 and undated (Box 4)
    - Wegner Associates, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Specialty Vacations, 3
    - General, 2002-2005 (Box 4)
    - Abercrombie & Kent--Family, 2004-2006 (Box 4)
    - Abercrombie & Kent--General, 1986-2006 (Box 4)
    - Abercrombie & Kent--General, 1986-2006 (Box 5)
    - Academy for International Medical StudyTravel for Doctors, 2004 (Box 5)
    - Adventure/Ecotourism, 1985-2003 and undated (Box 5)
    - Backroads Travel Co., 2005 (Box 5)
    - Ballooning, 1999-2003 (Box 5)
    - Biking/Cycling, 1996-2006 (Box 5)
    - Cooking Schools, 1987-1997 (Box 5)
    - Cruises, 1965-2005 and undated (Box 5)
    - Equestrian, 1994-1998 and undated (Box 5)
    - Fishing, 1959-2004 and undated (Box 6)
    - Foreign language study, 1998 and undated (Box 6)
    - Gay/Lesbian, 2004 and undated (Box 6)
    - Golf--General, 1983-2003; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Golf--Links Magazine, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Golf--Mexico/Caribbean, 1981-2004 (Box 6)
    - Golf--Schools, 1993-2002 (Box 6)
    - Golf--Spain, undated (Box 6)
    - Golf--UK/Ireland, 1997-2004 and undated (Box 6)
    - Golf--U.S., 1989-2000 and undated (Box 7)
    - Gutsy Women tours, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Honeymoon/Romance, 1995-2006 (Box 7)
    - Indian/Eskimo/Aleut crafts, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Marketing Ahead/Heritage Tours, undated (Box 7)
    - Orient Express, 2006 (Box 7)
    - Rafting/Kayaking, 1992-2002 (Box 7)
    - Rascals in Paradise, undated (Box 7)
    - Scuba/Snorkling, 1985-1996 and undated (Box 7)
    - Spas--General, 1985-2003 (Box 7)
    - Spas--California, 1998-2000 and undated (Box 7)
    - Spas--Canyon Ranch, 1994-2005; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Spas--Europe, 1987-2000 and undated (Box 8)
    - Spas--Florida, 1995-1999 and undated (Box 8)
    - Spas--Miraval (Ariz.), 1998 and undated (Box 8)
    - Spas--Premier Spas Magazine, 2003-2004 (Box 8)
    - Spas--Rancho La Puerta (Mexico), 1999 and undated (Box 8)
    - Spas--Spafinder Magazine, 1999-2006 (Box 8)
    - Spas--U.S., 1992-2005 and undated (Box 9)
    - Sports travel, 2003-2006 (Box 9)
    - Starquest Expeditions, 2005-2006 (Box 9)
    - Student/Youth travel--General, 1999-2005 (Box 9)
    - Student/Youth travel--Contiki, 2000-2003 (Box 9)
    - Student/Youth travel--Gerber, 2000-2005 (Box 9)
    - Tennis, 1989 and undated (Box 9)
    - Trafalgar, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Trophy hunting: To Those Who Hunt (Jonas Bros.), circa 1960s (Box 9)
    - Villas--General, 1989-2001 (Box 9)
    - Villas--Caribbean, 1983-2002 and undated (Box 9)
    - Villas--Cuendet, 1995-1999 (Box 9)
    - Villas--Europe, 2005 and undated (Box 10)
    - Villas--Villa Leisure, undated (Box 10)
    - Villlas--Villas of the World, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Walking/Hiking, 1998-2006 (Box 10)
    - Yacht/Sailing, 2001 and undated (Box 10)
    - Zegraham Tours, 1992-2003 (Box 10)
  - Transportation Services, 4
    - Airlines, 1980-1990 (Box 10)
    - Car/Limousine rental--General, 1994-2004 and undated (Box 10)
    - Car/Limousine rental--Budget Rent-a-Car, 1987-2005 and undated (Box 10)
    - Car/Limousine rental--Hertz, 1997-2004 (Box 10)
    - Car/Limousine rental--Kemwell, 1993-1997 (Box 10)
    - Motor homes, 1975-1987 and undated (Box 10)
    - Rail lines, 2002-2006 (Box 10)
- Africa, 1961-2006 and undated; 2; 6 boxes
  - General Files, 5
    - General, 1963-2006 and undated; 5 folders (Box AFR1)
    - Africa/Antarctica, 1985 (Box AFR1)
    - Central and West Africa, 1975-1977 and undated (Box AFR1)
    - East and Southern Africa, 1984-2005 (Box AFR1)
    - Safari/Ecotourism, 1970s-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box AFR2)
    - Travel (Air and rail), 1981 and undated (Box AFR2)
    - Travel (Air and rail)--Rovos Rail, 1995-2003 (Box AFR2)
  - Botswana, 6
    - General, 1986-1998 and undated (Box AFR2)
  - Egypt (Includes Sinai), 7
    - General, 1981-1990 and undated (Box AFR2)
    - Destinations, 1985 and undated (Box AFR2)
    - Hotels, 1975-2004 (Box AFR3)
    - Maps, 1960s-1990s (Box AFR3)
  - Ethiopa, 8
    - General, 1966-1980s (Box AFR3)
  - Gabon, 9
    - Hotels, 1975 (Box AFR3)
  - Ghana, 10
    - Hotels, undated (Box AFR3)
  - Ivory Coast, 11
    - General, 1973-1975 and undated (Box AFR3)
  - Kenya, 12
    - General, 1981-1991 and undated (Box AFR3)
    - Destinations/Safari, 1973-2003 and undated (Box AFR3)
    - Hotels, 1969-1993 and undated (Box AFR3)
    - Maps, 1972-1979 and undated (Box AFR3)
    - Safari Diary (Kathy Eldon), 1987 (Box AFR3)
  - Madagascar, 13
    - General, 1965-1974 (Box AFR4)
  - Mauritius, 14
    - General, 1987-2000s (Box AFR4)
  - Morocco, 15
    - General, 1965-2001 and undated; 3 folders (Box AFR4)
    - Destinations, 1963-1971 and undated (Box AFR4)
    - Destinations--Marrakech, 1991-2002 and undated (Box AFR4)
    - Hotels, 1964-2000 and undated (Box AFR4)
    - Maps, undated (Box AFR4)
  - Mozambique, 16
    - Hotels, undated (Box AFR4)
  - Namibia, 17
    - General, 1984-2001 and undated (Box AFR4)
  - Nigeria, 18
    - General, undated (Box AFR4)
  - Senegal, 19
    - General, 1970-1981 and undated; 2 folders (Box AFR4)
  - Seychelles, 20
    - General, 1979-1991 and undated (Box AFR4)
  - South Africa, 21
    - General, 1964-2003 and undated; 4 folders (Box AFR4)
    - Destinations, 1968-1994 and undated; 2 folders (Box AFR5)
    - Hotels, 1984-1995 (Box AFR5)
    - Hotels--Capetown, 1967-2002 and undated (Box AFR5)
    - Hotels--Johannesburg, 2004 and undated (Box AFR5)
    - Hotels--Paarl, 1994 and undated (Box AFR5)
    - HotelsPlettenburg Bay, undated (Box AFR5)
    - Maps, 1961-1980s; 2 folders (Box AFR5)
    - South African Tourist Board (Satour) publications, 1970s-1990s (Box AFR5)
    - South African Tourist Board (Satour) publications, 1970s-1990s (Box AFR6)
    - Tunisia, 24
      - General, 1973-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box AFR6)
      - Destinations, 1972-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box AFR6)
      - Hotels, 1973 and undated (Box AFR6)
      - Maps, 1982 and undated (Box AFR6)
      - Promo Tunisia itineraries, 2004 (Box AFR6)
      - Tunisian cook book, 1973 (Box AFR6)
  - Tanzania, 22
    - General, 1965 and undated (Box AFR6)
  - Togo, 23
    - Another Way to Africa (Peter Nichols), 1989 (Box AFR6)
  - Zambia
    - General, 1982 and undated; 2 folders (Box AFR6)
  - Zimbabwe/Rhodesia, 25
    - General, 1968-1990s (Box AFR6)
- Asia (Includes Middle East), 1942-2006 and undated; 3; 16 boxes
  - General Files, 26
    - General, 1982-2006; 3 folders (Box ASA1)
  - Afghanistan, 27
    - Kabul hotels, undated (Box ASA1)
  - Bahrain, 28
    - General, 1974-1992 (Box ASA1)
  - Bhutan, 29
    - General, 1975-1990s; 2 folders (Box ASA1)
  - Burma/Myanmar, 30
    - General, 1959-2005; 2 folders (Box ASA1)
  - Cambodia, 31
    - General, undated (Box ASA1)
    - Angkor, 1992 and undated (Box ASA1)
  - China (People's Republic), 32
    - General, 1979-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA1)
    - Agent Manual for Great China Tours, undated (Box ASA1)
    - Cities, undated (Box ASA2)
    - Destinations, 1980-1994 and undated (Box ASA2)
    - Hotels, 1986-2004 and undated (Box ASA2)
    - Hong Kong--General, 1967-1996 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA2)
    - Hong Kong--Hotels, 1990-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA2)
    - Hong Kong--Maps, 1980s-1994 (Box ASA3)
    - Hong Kong--Sightseeing/Events, 1985-1996 (Box ASA3)
    - Macau, 1966-1994 and undated (Box ASA3)
    - Provinces and regions, 1984 and undated (Box ASA3)
    - Sightseeing, undated (Box ASA3)
  - Dubai, 33
    - General, 2006 and undated (Box ASA3)
  - Himalayas (Includes IndiaNepalBhutanTibet), 34
    - General, 1967-2005; 2 folders (Box ASA3)
  - India, 35
    - General (Includes information on NepalSri LankaBhutan), 1957-1984 and undated (Box ASA3)
    - General, 1954-2006; 3 folders (Box ASA4)
    - General--India/Nepal, 1997-2005 (Box ASA4)
    - Cities--Delhi, 1958-1968 (Box ASA4)
    - Cities--Other, 1957 and undated (Box ASA4)
    - Destinations A-Z, 1958-1982 and undated (Box ASA4)
    - Destinations--Department of Tourism brochures, 1978-1982 (Box ASA4)
    - Destinations--Events, 1962-2005 (Box ASA4)
    - Hotels, 1950s-2005 (Box ASA5)
    - Hotels--Oberoi, 1973-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA5)
    - Hotels--Taj Group, 1972-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA5)
    - Hotels and maps, 1966-1975 and undated (Box ASA5)
    - Maps, 1962-1981 and undated (Box ASA6)
    - Regions and sightseeing, 1957-1975 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA6)
    - Tourism and travel agent materials, 1970-1980 (Box ASA6)
  - Indonesia, 36
    - General, 1966-1995 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA6)
    - General--Destinations, 1970s-2002 and undated (Box ASA6)
    - General--Hotels, 1995 and undated (Box ASA6)
    - Bali--General, 1969-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA6)
    - Bali--Hotels, 1981-2002 and undated (Box ASA6)
    - Bali--Hotels, 1981-2002 and undated (Box ASA7)
    - Irian Jaya, 1970s (Box ASA7)
    - Java, 1981 and undated (Box ASA7)
  - Iran, 37
    - General, 1966-1979 and undated (Box ASA7)
  - Israel, 38
    - General, 1942-2000 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA7)
    - Destinations, 1980-1997 and undated (Box ASA7)
    - Destinations--Ministry of Tourism literature, 1979-1998 and undated (Box ASA7)
    - Hotels, 1979-1994 and undated (Box ASA7)
    - Hotels--Dans (chain), 1992-1998 and undated (Box ASA8)
    - Hotels--Eilat, 1994-2000 and undated (Box ASA8)
    - Hotels--Jerusalem, 1974-1994 and undated (Box ASA8)
    - Hotels--Kibbutz/Guest house, 1987 and undated (Box ASA8)
    - Hotels--Tel Aviv, 1973-2000 and undated (Box ASA8)
    - Maps, 1980-2000 and undated (Box ASA8)
  - Japan, 39
    - General, 1957-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA8)
    - General, 1957-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA9)
    - General--ADA Handbook Japan and Hong Kong, 1969 (Box ASA9)
    - General--Japan Air Lines brochures, 1979-1981 and undated (Box ASA9)
    - Destinations, 1957-1993 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA9)
    - Destinations--Kyoto/Nara, undated (Box ASA9)
    - Hotels, 1957-1975 and undated (Box ASA9)
    - Hotels, 1978-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA10)
    - Hotels--Kyoto, 1969-1996 and undated (Box ASA10)
    - Hotels--Ryokan, 1970-1997 and undated (Box ASA10)
    - Hotels--Tokyo, 1966-1996 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA10)
    - Maps, 1977-1991 and undated (Box ASA10)
  - Jordan, 40
    - General, 1978 and undated (Box ASA11)
  - Korea/South Korea, 41
    - General, 1974-1994 and undated; 3 folders (Box ASA11)
    - Destinations, 1979-1994 and undated (Box ASA11)
    - Hotels, 1977-1995 and undated (Box ASA11)
    - Maps, 1994 and undated (Box ASA11)
  - Kuwait, 42
    - Hotels, 1972 and undated (Box ASA11)
  - Laos, 43
    - General, 1994 and undated (Box ASA11)
  - Lebanon, 44
    - General, 1966-2002 and undated (Box ASA11)
  - Malaysia, 45
    - General, 1969-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA11)
    - General, 1969-2001 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Destinations, 1998-2001 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Destinations--Borneo, 1987 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Destinations--Sport/Adventure, 1990-1992 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Hotels, 1997 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Hotels--Kuala Lampur, 1987-1999 and undated (Box ASA12)
    - Maps, undated (Box ASA12)
  - Maldives, 46
    - Hotels, 2001-2004 and undated (Box ASA12)
  - Middle East region, 47
    - General, 1980 and undated (Box ASA12)
  - Nepal, 48
    - General, 1982-1997 and undated (Box ASA12)
  - Pakistan, 49
    - General (Includes information on Iran, Turkey), 1968-1985 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA12)
  - Philippines, 50
    - General, 1960s-1985 and undated (Box ASA13)
    - Hotels, 1961-2002 (Box ASA13)
  - Saudi Arabia, 51
    - Hotels, 2001 (Box ASA13)
  - Singapore, 52
    - General, 1969-2003 and undated; 4 folders (Box ASA13)
    - Hotels, 1972-1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA14)
    - Hotels--Raffles, 1999-2002 and undated (Box ASA14)
    - Maps, 1987-2002 (Box ASA14)
    - Travel Agent Manual, 1996 (Box ASA14)
  - Sri Lanka/Ceylon, 53
    - General, 1950s-1982 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA14)
  - Taiwan/Formosa, 54
    - General, 1960-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA14)
    - Hotels, 1979-1996 and undated (Box ASA14)
  - Thailand, 55
    - General, 1969-1996 and undated (Box ASA14)
    - General, 1969-1996 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA15)
    - Convention guides, 1993-1994 (Box ASA15)
    - Destinations, 1983-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA15)
    - Events and festivals, 1992-1996 (Box ASA15)
    - Hotels, 1990-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box ASA15)
    - Hotels--Mandarin Oriental, 1992-2005 and undated (Box ASA16)
    - Hotels--Sukothai, 1991-2003 (Box ASA16)
    - Maps, 1996 and undated (Box ASA16)
    - Travel guides, 1988-1995 (Box ASA16)
    - Travel guides--Royal Orchid, 1991-1998 (Box ASA16)
  - Tibet, 56
    - Tibet: The High & Fragile Land Behind the Ranges (S. Dillon Ripley), 1980 (Box ASA16)
  - United Arab Emirates, 57
    - Hotels, 1973 (Box ASA16)
  - Vietnam/Indochina, 58
    - General, 1995-2003 (Box ASA16)
    - Hotels, 2000-2007 and undated (Box ASA16)
    - Tours--Trails of Indochina, 2004-2005 (Box ASA16)
    - Tours--Vidotour, 1997-1998 (Box ASA16)
  - Yemen, 59
    - General, 1984 (Box ASA16)
- Canada, 1968-2006 and undated; 4; 6 boxes
  - General Files, 60
    - General information, 1968-1976 (Box CAN1)
    - Bus tours, 1997-2003 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Heli-Adventures, 2000-2006 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Maps, 1996 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Rail tours, 1995-2006 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Tour/Travel information, 1978-2006; 2 folders (Box CAN1)
  - Alberta, 61
    - General, 1986-2006 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Banff, 1987-2006 and undated (Box CAN1)
    - Calgary, 1977-2003 (Box CAN1)
    - Edmonton, 1986-2005 (Box CAN1)
    - Hotels, 1993-2004 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Jasper, 1989-2002 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Maps, 1977-1997 and undated (Box CAN2)
  - British Columbia, 62
    - General, 1987-2005 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Hotels, 1993-2005 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Vancouver, 1987-1994 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Vancouver--Hotels, 1991-1999 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Victoria, 1990-2004 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Victoria--Butchart Gardens, 1991-1999 (Box CAN2)
    - Victoria--Hotels, 1984-2002 (Box CAN2)
    - Maps, 1986-1994 and undated (Box CAN2)
    - Whistler, 1992-2001 and undated (Box CAN3)
  - Manitoba, 63
    - General, undated (Box CAN3)
    - Adventure/Fishing, 1985-2005 (Box CAN3)
    - Hotels, 2002-2004 and undated (Box CAN3)
    - Winnipeg, 1980-1986 and undated (Box CAN3)
  - New Brunswick, 64
    - General, 1975-2002 and undated (Box CAN3)
    - Hotels, 1950s-1987 and undated (Box CAN3)
  - Newfoundland/Labrador, 65
    - General, 1973 and undated (Box CAN3)
  - Northwest Territories, 66
    - General, 1979-1990 and undated (Box CAN3)
  - Nova Scotia, 67
    - General, 1990-2004 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Hotels, 1987-1991 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Maps, 1966-1991 and undated (Box CAN4)
  - Ontario, 68
    - General, 1987-2002 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Destinations, 1980-2004 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Hotels, 1979-1999 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Maps, 1974-1999 and undated (Box CAN4)
    - Muskoka, 1982-1986 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Niagara Falls, 1972-2005 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Ottawa, 1972-1999 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Toronto, 1977-2004 and undated (Box CAN5)
  - Prince Edward Island, 69
    - General, 1982-1988 and undated (Box CAN5)
  - Quebec, 70
    - General, 1984-1999 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Destinations, 1981-1995 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Hotels, 1980-2004 and undated (Box CAN5)
    - Hotels, 1980-2004 and undated (Box CAN6)
    - Maps, 1972-1999 (Box CAN6)
    - Montreal, 1978-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAN6)
    - Montreal--Hotels, 1981-1997 and undated (Box CAN6)
  - Rockies, 71
    - General, 1976-2006 and undated (Box CAN6)
  - Saskatchewan, 72
    - General, 1971-1988 and undated (Box CAN6)
  - Yukon, 73
    - General, 1986-1991 (Box CAN6)
- Caribbean, 1947-2006 and undated; 5; 13 boxes
  - General Files, 74
    - General, 1947-2004; 2 folders (Box CAR1)
    - General--Villas, 1997-2006 and undated (Box CAR1)
  - Angulla, 75
    - General, 1992-2004 and undated (Box CAR1)
    - Cap Juluca, 1991-1999 and undated (Box CAR1)
  - Antigua
    - General, 1965-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box CAR1)
  - Aruba, 76
    - General, 1963-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR1)
  - Bahamas, 77
    - General, 1966-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR2)
    - Hotels and sightseeing, 1965-1980 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR2)
    - Abaco, 1980-2004 and undated (Box CAR2)
    - Andros, 1971-1992 and undated (Box CAR2)
    - Eleuthera, 1972-1994 and undated (Box CAR2)
    - Exuma, 1975-2005 and undated (Box CAR2)
    - Grand Bahama, 1970-2004 and undated (Box CAR2)
    - Grand Bahama, 1970-2004 and undated (Box CAR3)
    - Grand Bahama--Lucaya, 1967-1987 and undated (Box CAR3)
    - Harbour Island, 1966-2002 and undated (Box CAR3)
    - Long Island, 1978-1991 and undated (Box CAR3)
    - Musha Cay, circa 2002 (Box CAR3)
    - Nassau, 1977-1997 and undated (Box CAR3)
    - Nassau--Hotels, 1978-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR3)
    - Paradise Island, 1978-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR3)
    - Paradise Island--Atlantis, 1999-2003 and undated (Box CAR4)
  - Barbados, 78
    - General, 1962-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR4)
    - Hotels, 1984-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR4)
  - Bermuda
    - General, 1964-1980 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR4)
    - General, 1996-2005 and undated (Box CAR5)
    - Activities/Sightseeing, 1989-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR5)
    - Golf, 1989-2000 and undated (Box CAR5)
    - Hotels, 1983-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR5)
    - Hotels--Cambridge Beach, 1997-2004 and undated (Box CAR5)
    - Hotels--Cottages, 1984-2001 and undated (Box CAR5)
    - Maps, 1985-2003 and undated (Box CAR5)
  - Bonaire, 79
    - General, 1957-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR5)
  - Canouan, 80
    - General, undated (Box CAR6)
  - Cayman Islands, 81
    - General, 1967-2006 and undated; 3 folders (Box CAR6)
    - Diving/Water sports, 1989-2000 and undated (Box CAR6)
    - Hotels, 1984-2005 and undated (Box CAR6)
    - Hotels--Villas, 1994-1996 and undated (Box CAR6)
    - Maps, 1995-2003 and undated (Box CAR6)
  - Cuba, 82
    - General, 1978 (Box CAR6)
  - Curacao, 83
    - General, 1963-2004 and undated (Box CAR6)
  - Dominican Republic, 84
    - General, 1974-1976 and undated (Box CAR6)
    - General, 2002-2005 and undated (Box CAR7)
  - Grenada, 85
    - General, 1961-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR7)
  - Grenadines, 86
    - General, 2005 and undated (Box CAR7)
  - Guadeloupe, 87
    - General, 1969-1977 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR7)
  - Haiti, 88
    - General, 1982 and undated (Box CAR7)
  - Jamaica, 89
    - General, 1961-2003 and undated; 3 folders (Box CAR7)
    - Golf, 1986-2003 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts, 1990-2005 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Kingston, 1990 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Montego Bay, 1992-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Negril, 1985-2000 and undated (Box CAR8)
    - Hotels/Resorts--Negril--Couples, 1997-1998 and undated (Box CAR8)